Previously on This Is Us...
《我的生活》前情提要
I wanted to be the man that made you happy.
我想成樽你幸福的男人
From here on out, I'm gonna be a 12 for you.
默F在_始  我要做12分的好丈夫
You are getting in the car right now,
你F在立刻上
and we are going to this doctors appointment.
然后我去@位t生
Hi, white people.
白人
I don't know what you were looking for with all this,
我不知道你做@些事是榱耸裁
but I do know you don't have a whole lot of time.
但我知道你的rg和精力是有限的
I'd like to tell the girls who you are.
我想跟孩子f出你的身份
I was not a very good brother to you, was I?
δ碚f  我不是好哥哥  是
No, you weren't.
你不是
But you still got time.
但你有rga
- Toby. ?- Kate.
-我叫托比  -我叫P特
How's your breakfast?
早餐怎么
You mean this, uh, steel-cut oatmeal and egg-white pancake
你是f你做的@粗切燕
you're making me eat? It's amazing.
有u蛋煎  太好吃了
I'm gonna do theater.
我要去演
I did it-- I-I-
我I票了
I booked a redeye to New York.
我了去~s的夜g航班
It's a scorcher out there, folks.
各位  匹堡市今天很
- Stay cool, Pittsburgh. - ?Shut up.
-大家注意避暑  -]嘴
Don't tell me to shut up.
e我]嘴
- You're doing it wrong. - No, I'm not.
-你的玩法不  -我]玩e
- Yes, you are. - Mom, I'm hot.
-你就是e了  -  好
I know, kiddo. Dad is trying to fix the air conditioning.
我知道  孩子  爸爸在修空{了
Babe, how's it going? We're dying in here.
修得怎么恿  我快崴懒
I'm working on it.
我在努力
Give it back!
o我
- Just hold on. ?- Enough!
-你等等  -蛄
Mom, Randall took my Rubik's Cube.
m德了我的魔方
- You weren't doing it right. - Enough. Come here.
-你玩e了  -好了  我看
You did this?
你Q出淼
You're supposed to be yelling at him!
你吼他才
Randall, stop scratching.
m德  不要狭
That's a rash, babe. You're gonna make it worse.
你起了皮疹  越抓越乐
Okay, I think I have a solution.
好的  我想到k法了
Is it fixed? Jack, what...
修好了  杰克  你怎么...
What are you doing wearing that shirt? You know I hate that shirt.
你怎么穿了@件  你明知道我不喜g
I'm wearing this shirt because it makes me think of fun.
我穿@件是因榇┲就很_心
It makes me think of sun.
穿著就想到光
And because we are going to the pool!
因槲要去游泳啦
Kate Pearson, you get in here
P特・皮森  快^
and you strut your stuff, young lady.
秀出你的好身材  小美女
That's right.
]e
- Care Bears. ?- You know it, you know it.
-坌男  -]e就是@  就@
Today, people, we are gonna debut
都好了  今天就是
the brand-new Care Bear bikini!
坌男鼙然尼的女秀
Can we go to the Greenview pool?
能不能去G茵泳池
The one with the diving board? Please.
跳水板的那  好不好
No, that place sucks.
不行  那地方太了
You barely get in anyway. ?
反正你也基本不下水
The Big Three. Your brother needs you.
三小家伙  你弟弟需要你
Come on, you big mope.
e不妨艘黄鹑グ
Don't hold out on us.
eG下我
Please. Please.
求你了  求你了
Okay, okay, yes.
好  好  去吧
- Go get your swimsuits on. - Go get your suits.
-去Q泳衣  -快去吧
Come on, towels, towels.
e忘了拿毛巾  毛巾
AC is zonked, babe, we're gonna have to call someone.
空{完全炝  得找人硇
Pool, huh? Not a movie?
去游泳  不看影
Are you sure you're okay with the pool today.
_定你今天能去游泳池
We're gonna have a day-long pool vacation.
我要去泳池度一天假
I'm gonna snag us
我
not one, not two,
不是一  也不是
- but five pool chairs. - Five?
-而是五游泳椅  -五
I'm gonna snag us five pool chairs.
我要去五游泳椅
- You bad man. - ?Yes, I am.
-你可真  -必的
The kids are gonna run off,
孩子自己跑去玩
you're gonna finish that book you've been
你就可以趁此C看完赡砟阋恢
Oh, it's gonna be fun.
怎么  一定很有意思的
No, no, no,
不不不
the book is Misery, by Stephen King.
是f名叫《一迷》  史蒂芬・金的
Oh, yeah, right.
@影
Hey, I already packed the cooler.
我已把冷鱿溲b好了
All soft drinks, no beer.
只э料  不拿啤酒
A whole day at the pool with those kids and no beer?
跟@秃⒆釉谟境卮一天不拿啤酒
I told you, I stopped drinking.
我f^  我戒酒了
It's not you I'm worried about.
我心的可不是你
See? That's what we need, then.
你看  那就更去了
We just need a day to relax.
我需要放松一天
A reminder, there is no running,
剀疤崾  泳池禁止奔跑打[
no diving, and absolutely no glass containers in the pool area.
禁止水  勿yРＡ器皿M入泳池
Feeling relaxed yet?
放松了
There's a chair!
有椅子
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
快跑  快跑
Go get it! Get it, yes!
快  太棒了
Get it, get it, get it. ?Yeah!
到  到  太好了
Oh, stop it. That doesn't hurt.
e叫  才根本不疼
Oh, that one might've hurt.
我好像真弄疼你了
Sorry. Gotcha.
抱歉  乖啦
I want Grandpa to do mine.
我想o我梳^l
No problem, Miss Annie.
]}  安妮小姐
Oh, really? You want Grandpa to try to tame this mess?
你要硎帐斑@一^剪不嗬磉y
- Have at it. - Let's see here.
-那就戆  -我看看啊
Oh, that's gotta go. Beth, where's your scissors?
@肯定得剪了  z  剪刀在哪里
No! ?
不要
Then you better sit still and not give me a hard time.
那你得坐了  不Sy槲
How'd you get that scar?
那道疤是怎么回事
Oh, that? Rock, bottle...
@啊  那天...
there were plenty in the air that day.
石K  瓶子到yw
Maybe we don't tell that story.
@故事是不要v了
Oh, no, it's not a bad one.
]事  @故事挺不e的
and I was helping out with that.
我也去兔Τ隽α
'86, '87?
那是86是87年
What's bussing?
什么是校接送制度
Getting poor children into the schools
就是F人的孩子也能
in better neighborhoods.
去好W校上W
You were working with the Urban League?
你在城市盟工作^
Yeah, a little bit, yeah.
是  有段rg
Look, I gotta get on my walk.
我要去散步了
You wanna take over here?
接下砟憷^m
Okay, you two, let's get moving.
好了  你z  悠戆
Mom and I gotta get to work
我和要去上班了
so we can pay for all this hair product.
不然可]XI各N美la品了
- The Eagle has landed. - What's up?
-雄著了  -什么情r
I'm officially a New Yorker now-- East Coast!
我正式身~s客了  |海岸fq
Hey, somebody wants to say hi.
有人要跟你打招呼
Uncle Kevin, come see my play.
P文叔叔  砜次业谋硌莅
I'm Snow White.
我演白雪公主哦
You're kidding me!
你]_我吧
Snow White's my favorite character of all time!
白雪公主是我一直以碜鄣慕巧呢
I'm actually auditioning for a play, too.
其我也在橐鲅莩鲈R呢
Yeah, it's very dark, very, very truthful--
鼍胺浅０  也非常接近生活--
- Do the Manny voice. - What's that?
-快W下奶爸的音  -什么
They love it when you do the catchphrase.
他喜g你f那句口^U
I don't want to do the Manny voice.
我不想再W奶爸的音了
- Please. ?- Please.
-拜托嘛  -拜托
- Baby say what? - ?Like, for real.
-f什么  -再像一c
Baby say what?
f什么啊
No, like in the show.
不  要像里那
Your biggest fans.
超粉z啊
Any... Anyway, this play is a total departure for me,
不^不管怎  我已氐赘e@部×
you know?
知道
None of that, like, Manny stuff.
奶爸什么的  都一刀嗔
It's a character-driven departure for me.
@ξ碚f是≈腥宋锏母e
Where'd you go? What are you looking at?
你在  你看什么呢
Hey, man, uh, I gotta go.
兄弟  我得炝
You're just gonna hang up on him?
你就@焖啊
No, no, no, I will not show you my I.D.
不不不  我不o你看身份C的
Not until you tell me why you need a reason to see it.
除非你告V我  你槭裁匆看
Tony, what's going on here?
托尼  l生什么事了
Hey, Mr. Pearson. We had a report of someone loitering.
皮森先生  有人e笏四徘徊
I wasn't loitering.
我]有四徘徊
I was taking my walk, and literally
我是在散步
on my way to smell the roses,
_切地f是去品味玫瑰花香
- as I have been for the past week. - ?I know.
-就像上周一  -我知道
Is there some local rose smelling ordinance
@里y道有什么禁止p花的法律
- I'm not aware of? - ?William, enough.
-我]f的  -威廉  蛄
Enough...
蛄
He's with you, sir?
他是和你一起的  先生
Yeah, he's staying with us.
是的  他和我住一起
- Sorry. ?- Sorry?
-不好意思  -不好意思
We're so sorry.
我很抱歉
We didn't know, Randall.
我不知道情r  m德
Understood. Thanks.
明白  xx
Thank you, Tony.
xx你  托尼
We're gonna get you some new clothes.
我得o你I些新衣服了
I hate kale.
我甘{
Me, too.
我也是
Baby arugula is just as bad as grown-up arugula.
小芝麻菜和大芝麻菜一与y吃
All right, you know what?
算了
Here we go.
我I伟
Oh, no, no, no. Let me get--
不行  不行  我...
Remember, you are unemployed.
e忘了  你失I了
And I am not convinced that you would do well
而且我也不信你能
- begging for money. - Are you kidding?
-靠乞度日  -你在_玩笑
You don't think the drivers will be sympathetic to me
你不X得司C要是看到
holding up a sign that says "Hungry?"
我e著"]吃"的牌子很同情我
That's good.
那就好
I'm gonna use the restroom, and then we'll go, okay?
我去下l生g  然后就走  行
How are you?
你^得怎么
- Uh, good. How are you? - ?Good.
-挺好的  你呢  -不e
Okay, uh... you wanna get out of here?
好了  你要走了
- Who was that? ?- Who was...
-那是l  -哪
You saw that. Uh, that was my ex-wife.
你看到了啊  那是我前妻
Wait, are you serious?
等下  你是f真的
Yeah. I told you I was married before.
是啊  我跟你f^我Y^婚
Not to that.
可]f是@N
Supermodel, pose... and catwalk.
超模砹  [姿萘  再碡步
Hey, Kate, stop being silly.
P特  e傻了
Come over here, please.
快^
Samantha and Vicki are here!
_曼莎和薇琪也砹
- Care Bears! - Okay, that's two.
-坌男  -好了  椅子了
Babe, I had to sleep with someone to get this one.
H鄣  我是出u肉w才Q淼囊巫
- I hope that's okay. - Yeah, I'm fine with it.
-希望你原我  -我]}啊
As long as his wife is okay with it.
只要他老婆不介意就好
Kevin, you're up, please. Shirt off.
P文  到你了  把衣服了
Why? I don't even like swimming.
槭裁  我都不塾斡
You don't have to put your face in.
你不一定^也要下去
You can sit in the shallow end and Randall will stay with you.
你可以待在\水^  m德陪你的
I don't like Randall either.
我也不喜gm德
- Hey, Kev, come on. - Enough.
-小P  干嘛呢  -ef了
Turn around.
D^去
Randall, you're up, please.
m德  到你了
Come here.
^戆
Turn around, please.
D身
Are you sure I really need sunscreen?
你_定我需要涂防袼
- Yes, absolutely. ?- Yeah, absolutely.
-肯定要  -要啊  然
Of course you do. Sure.
你然要涂了
Okay, look, Big Three, come here.
三小家伙  快^
Come here. You are surrounded by adults
^  你周有很多大人
and lifeguards that resemble adults.
和同邮谴笕说木壬T
There's very little trouble you can actually get into--
你不遇上...
Wait, wait. Kate, baby,
等等  等下  P特
are you sure you don't want to put a shirt on?
你_定不再套件衣服
- Right. - ?Here.
-好吧  -o
Enjoy your Misery.
好好看你的吧
People are staring at her in that bathing suit, Jack.
大家都盯著她的泳衣看  杰克
Some jerky little kid is gonna say something.
那些小混球一定f三道四的
It's baby fat.
那只是悍
She's only eight years old. Kids haven't turned mean yet.
她才八q  孩子@菏裁炊疾欢
And what is up with Kevin lately, and that attitude?
P文最近是怎么了  B度那么差
- He's so jealous of Randall. - He's fine.
-他太嫉妒m德了  -他]事
Babe, he's fine. They are all fine.
他]事  他仨都很好
And does Randall need sunscreen?
有m德需要抹防袼
I mean, have we just been wasting sunscreen all of these years?
@些年砦都是在他身上浪M防袼
That I have no answer for.
@我也不知道
Chair. Chair!
椅子  椅子
Careful!
小心c
She's his ex-wife, Kate.
她只是他的前妻  P特
All right? The operative word being "Ex."
好  PI字是"前"
They're not together anymore. He's with you now.
他已x婚了  他F在和你在一起
"Why?" is the question. You should see her.
可槭裁茨  你真瞧瞧她
Maybe that's what Toby wants.
也S那才是托比想要的
Maybe he's fulfilling a fat-girl fetish with me.
也S他看上我是榱M足他的胖妞癖
Well, that's actually a thing.
_有@N癖好
Of course, for me it was
然  ξ碚f
more of a phase than a thing, but anyway...
那更像是一A段  但也差不多
I did a deep dive with this woman.
我仔{查了下@女人
Everything reeks fabulous.
她的一切都如此完美
She has fabulous taste, she has fabulous friends.
完美的品位  完美的朋友
She's been to Argentina, Kevin!
她去^阿根廷  P文
Listen to me, I did not leave you in Los Angeles
我f  我把你留在洛杉
so you could self-sabotage, okay?
不是你自我糟`的
So get off the Internet-- do that right now--
所以so把WP掉  立刻R上
and tell me how hard I'm gonna crush this audition.
告V我怎么做才能通^R
The edges are gone...
消失了
and then the thing.
事情也S之l生了
Thank you, Sean Patrick.
xx你  肖恩・帕特里克
Some good choices, I thought.
我X得有人挺不e
It's Daniel. Everyone else sucks.
丹尼不e  其他人演得透了
You know, I kind of liked--
其我更喜g...
It's Daniel.
就x丹尼
Hold on, hold on.
稍等  稍等
We have one more. Kevin Pearson.
有一位  P文・皮森
Sorry. I know, I know. I'm sorry. I'm sorry I'm late.
Σ黄  我知道  很抱歉我t到了
It's just, you know, I tried to take the subway, right,
我本硐胱地F  再一路走^
and then walk, like a New Yorker.
像~s客那
Ron Shiller.
我是_恩・希勒
This is Sloane Sandberg.
@位是斯隆・桑德伯格
- You're the, uh, screenwriter. - Playwright.
-你就是  -∽骷
Well, you know, I mean, you gotta start somewhere.
你是要~出第一步的
You'll be reading with Miss Maine today, if that's okay.
今天你和梅英小姐  如果你不介意的
Yeah, no, whatever you got, you know.
然  和l都行
Miss Maine, Miss Iowa.
因州小姐  酆扇A州小姐
I judged, uh, Miss USA for Trump once,
我曾ux^支持特朗普美小姐
so we may have actually met before.
所以我可能^面
Miss Maine is Olivia Maine.
梅英小姐全名是W利S・梅英
Tony nominee.
托尼提名@得者
She plays Jessica.
她扮演杰西卡
Of course. Hi. Good to meet you.
然  你好  很高dJR你
Well, before we start, I just wanted to...
在_始之前  我有...
I want to get something off my chest.
我有拙湓必要f
I do understand the perception, you know.
我知道你的看法
These L.A. actors, they come out here, right?
洛杉的演T淼竭@里
They do their little quick stint in theater
≡豪镫S便演小角色
just to feel better about themselves.
只M足自己的s心
That's not why I'm here, okay?
而我s不是  好
I'm here for the right reasons.
我磉@是有正理由的
Let's get this over with, shall we?
那我so把@ν臧  可以
Did you want me to start?
你想我先_始
Yes, I thought it would be good, if,
]e  我X得那颖容^好
you speak, then I speak,
你先f  我后f
then you speak, and we all go home.
接著你再f  然后我就可以回家了
Does that work for you?
你X得可以
Yeah. That's great...
行啊  很好
My recollection's hazy, actually, it was a long day.
我的有c模糊了  @一天在太漫L了
Not for me. Mine was over before 9:00 in the morning.
我可不是  早上九c前我的一天就Y束了
That's really good... accent.
你的口音真棒
- What? - ?The American accent.
-你f什么  -美口音
What?
什么
I just... diving... diving right back in.
我正...  努力融入角色
It say, uh... it says "I lay," uh, I don't...
_~是...  "我躺在"  我不...
Let me just say... I don't need to say it. It says...
我f...我不需要f@  _~是...
I'll just say it.
我是f吧
I lay...
我躺在...
Just keep going.
^m^m
This is...
真是...
I'll get it.
我能搞定
I lay on the dock all night,
我整夜躺在a^上
and part of the next morning.
直至天明
And I don't feel a thing.
s感受不到任何|西
Let me take that again.
我再硪槐
Oh, my gosh... Oh, my gosh.
我的天  我的天
Okay. Baby say what...
好的  f什么...
Okay. I-I lay... Let me get into it.
好了  我躺在...  我j下
I lay on the dock all night and part of the next morning.
我整夜躺在a^上直至天明
And I don't feel a thing.
s感受不到任何|西
The bug bites, the sunburn. Nothin'.
蚊x叮咬  皮w  都]有感X
It's like when we used to go fishing. You remember?
就像我以前一起去~r  你得
- I never fished... - Do you have the next...
-我]^~  -你是下一句...
- What the hell? - ?Sorry.
-你搞什么鬼  -Σ黄
You weren't talking, so I thought...
你]f  我以...
It's called a pause.
@叫停D
Right.
是
Sorry. It doesn't say pause on my script...
抱歉  我的”旧]有停D...
Well, it doesn't say suck, either, yet here we are.
上面也]呢  可我F在不就是@
You know your size?
你知道你的尺a
Always tended toward the slim.
我是挑修身的穿
I don't see that changing much at this point.
估F在也]吧
Try these.
@些
Afterwards, we'll swing by the pharmacy,
完了我路去一趟店
get those medications that the doctor wrote for you.
把t生o你_的拿了
Sounds like a plan.
起硗好的
$100?
一百美元
It's what they cost.
就是@r
I'm paying, just take the pants.
我I  你就I吧
So are we gonna talk about it or not?
我要不要
Talk about what?
什么
About what. Uh, this morning.
什么  今天早上的事
Or are you content to stand in silent judgment with that face?
是你就想臭著s什么也不f
It's just my face.
我的平r就@
No, you didn't like me apologizing for you.
不  你是不喜g我替你道歉
I get it.
我懂
Would you have been happier if I made a big scene?
如果我把事情[大你是不是就高d了
You know, got up in Tony's face,
揍托尼一D
had the cops roll up and turn the hoses on us?
把警察招砣缓χ我水
It's the Cosgroves.
他是卡斯格拉夫一家
He runs an insurance agency, she collects owls.
先生_了一家保U公司  妻子收藏^
History would not have memorialized our stand.
v史可不站在我@一
You ever had a hose turned on you?
你被水^
Can't say that I have, I'm very sorry.
很抱歉  我]有^
Don't be. It hurts.
不要L  很疼的
And there's that face.
就是@表情
Only face I got. Look, I could use some socks...
我就是@N表情  我想I纂pm子
No, the face. The one that says I have a scar
@表情  就好像是在f你胳膊上
on my arm from integrating schools.
有年樗秃⒆上W留下的疤痕
And probably blisters on your feet from marching for freedom,
f不定_上有樽杂捎涡r留下的水泡
but me, because I grew up in a white house,
至于我  因槲页砷L于白人家庭
you think I don't live in a black man's world.
你就J槲也欢黑人的生活
Oh, you know the one.
你知道你是什么表情
The one where that salesman there has been eyeballing us
你的表情那IIT奈MT那一刻起
ever since we came in here.
就一直盯著我
Or where that security guard has moved just a little
有那保安的位置挪恿艘稽cc
off his mark so he can keep us in his sight.
只楦好地O我
And where they'll definitely ask
有他肯定在我付X的r候
for an ID with my credit card when I go to pay,
我出示信用卡的用糇C明
even though they haven't asked for anybody else's.
M管他]向其他人提出^@拥囊求
Plus a million things every day
再加上每天似@拥o导小事
that I have to choose to let go,
我都要xo
just so I'm not pissed off all the time.
@游也挪把自己馑
Like I did on the street this morning.
就像我今早在街上做的一
Like I have done every day of my life.
就和我每天做的事一
Now try on the damn slim cut flat front chinos.
快去你的修身o褶休e吧
I think they'll look nice on you.
你穿著肯定好看
Randall
m德
Watch!
看
Cool! Cool!
太酷了
Dad, watch! Dad!
爸  看我  爸
- Where's the other one? - I'm looking.
-另外一去哪毫  -我在找
Man, you take your eyes off one for a second,
天啊  只要一秒不盯著一
you lose track of the others.
其他的就也都不了
That's because there are more of them
那是因樗人
than there are of us.
比咱z多呀
Always will be.
永h都是@
What? Oh.
什么
Talking about the kids.
在f孩子呀
Yep. It's a war. They got the numbers.
是啊  他人多荼
- Dad! Dad! - We were beat before we started.
-爸爸  爸爸  -我]_始就累趴了
- Watch! - There she is.
-看我  -她在那耗
Hi. Hey, guys.
你好
You want to play mermaids?
想玩美人~
This is from all of us.
@是我所有人o你的
Dad!
爸爸
Dad! Daddy! Dad!
爸爸  爸爸
Dad, watch me!
爸爸  快看我
Yeah. I see you, pal!
好  我看你了
Do you remember the first time he said "Dad"?
得他第一次叫我爸爸的r候
How happy I was?
我有多高d
Now where's Randall?
m德去哪毫
How about that time? Did you see?
怎么  你看了
Hey, Kev. Where's your brother?
小P  你弟弟呢
I don't know!
我不知道
Jack.
杰克
You take land, I'll take sea.
你去岸上找  我看看水里
Dad! Watch!
爸爸  快看我
Kevin.
P文
You were supposed to watch each other!
你互相照看Ψ降
Randall!
m德
Kate, it was the worst audition
P特  @真是史上
in the history of the world. Okay?
最糟糕的一次面了
I mean, that woman made me so nervous,
那女的搞得我超o
I started doing an English accent
中途我居然oo故地
in the middle of it for no reason!
f起了英式口音
Okay, I'm sure it wasn't that bad.
肯定]有那么糟吧
Maybe that's the problem. You know?
也S@才是}所在
- I wanted it too much. - Hey! It's the Man-ny!
-我太想得到@角色了  -@不是奶爸
Hey Man-ny! How's it going?
奶爸  最近怎么
Yeah. Listen. Could you please fly out here?
著  你能不能坐wC^
I really need you right now.
我F在真的很需要你
You'll be fine, you just...
你]事的  只要...
What? I'm just what? Where'd you go?
我只要什么  怎么不f了
Nowhere. I'm here. I'm shopping.
]什么  我在逛街
- I'm lost. - You're not lost.
-我好迷茫  -你@不是迷茫
It's just all new. It's just new.
只是一切δ碚f都太陌生了
No... I mean I'm actually lost,
不是  我是f我真的迷路了
I have no idea where the hell I'm at. I got to go.
我完全不知道我F在在哪  我先炝
Sorry. Oh.
抱歉
That whole thing back there, just so you know.
l生的事  我想f
I'm not actually bad, okay?
我其]那么  好
- Okay. Duly noted. - Okay.
-好  我知道了  -好的
Okay. Just wanted to get that out there.
我只是想跟你f明白
Well, out there it is.
好了  你f完了
Although you weren't super helpful.
不^你也]有蜕鲜裁疵
You want to get a drink?
你想喝一杯
What, like, now?
F在
Yeah. Now. Come on,
]e  就F在  走吧
- L.A. - Yeah.
-洛杉男孩  -好
Mom, the play's about to start!
演出快_始了
All right, Tess. Hurry up.
好吧  苔z  快c
Go get your dress on. Get her shoes.
快去把裙子Q上  拿好她的鞋
- Hurry, hurry, hurry. - Break a leg.
-快快快  -祝你演出成功
Come on...
加油
This is a nice place.
@地方真不e
Yeah. Public schools in this area are good,
是啊  @片地^的公立W校很不e
It's why we moved here.
所以我才搬磉@里
Even better than private.
甚至比私立的更好
You know, the parents are real involved.
父母能完全⑴c到孩子的成L中
You know, Beth's on the board.
z是董事的一T
Real involved.
完全⑴c其中
They got a farm.
W校有r
- Really? - Yeah, out back.
-真的  -  就在教W呛竺
Kids learn about the land. Grow their own food.
孩子能蛄私馔恋  H手N植食物
Thank you.
xx
They got, uh, chickens.
r隼镞B了u
They got a goat.
有一^山羊
Can I help you find something?
需要椭
No.
不用
You're here about the job.
你是想工作的事吧
You know. The job?
我@里的招工啊
Y-Yeah.
]e
Great!
太好了
Let's go over here so we can talk.
那我去那聊一聊
Randall!
m德
Kate, have you seen Randall?
P特  你看m德了
Randall?
m德
Did you not hear me calling you?
你]到我叫你
- Hey, what are you doing over here? - Oh, no, no, no...
-你在@焊墒裁茨  -不不不
- I've been... - It's okay. I'm watching him.
-我到...  -]事的  我看著他呢
Okay, it's... I-I have him now. I'm sorry,
好的  F在有我碚疹他了  抱歉
I'm his mother. I was a little panicked. I'm Rebecca.
我是他  我差c牧  我叫卡
We know who you are.
我知道你是l
You do?
你知道
Oh yes. When a white family has a black child
]e  如果一白人家庭е一黑人小孩
and they don't introduce themselves to any of us,
也]有向我介B^自己
we tend to take notice.
我一般都多加注意
Well. Thank you for watching him.
xx你照看他
He's just not supposed to be over here.
只是他不在@旱
Not "over here" like that.
不是f@里有什么不好
There's nothing wrong with over here.
磉@]什么不
I just mean that I want him where we can see him,
我的意思是他待在我的范
where we're sitting, in front of us.
也就是我坐的地方  我面前
Thank you. It was very nice to meet you.
xx你  很高dJR你
Randall, come on. Let's go.
m德  戆  我走
Come on. Thank you.
戆  xx你
Actually, you stay right here.
等等  你在@等一下
That's my son, and I'm his mother.
那是我的鹤  我是他
And I don't know if you have
我不知道你是不是
some sort of problem with that arrangement,
@拥募彝ビ惺裁匆庖
but also, I don't really care.
但是我真的不在乎
Thank you very much for watching my son.
之xx你臀艺湛次的孩子
But I have him now.
但F在由我碚疹他了
- Okay. - Okay.
-好吧  -好的
You need to get the child a proper haircut.
你Ш⒆蛹粢合m的l型了
The razor bumps on his neck.
剃刀都把他脖子了
You need a barber who knows how to cut black hair.
你需要找知道怎么理黑人^l的理l店
Come on.
走吧
I told you to stay with your brother, didn't I?
我跟你f了你跟哥哥待在一起  不是
Sorry.
Σ黄
Is this the real reason you wanted to come to this pool
@就是你想磉@泳池  不去其它泳池的
and not the other?
真正原因
Come on.
走吧
So beautiful.
真美啊
Ho, there. Who might you be, fair maid?
您好呀  敢姑娘芳名
I am the Princess Snow White.
我是白雪公主
I have traveled this land and many others,
我周游四方
and never have I seen a beauty so fair.
奈匆^如此一位肌w如雪的美人
Where are you from, noble sir?
@位士  您又是哪睦砟
What errand brings you to the forest?
您淼竭@森林中又是所楹问履
I come from a land far away.
我碜赃bh之地
- The, uh... - Thank you.
-那...  -xx
That play is really special, isn't it?
那部≌娴暮芴e
I mean, I don't read a lot of plays,
我的意思是  m然我]有x^很多”
- but that's -- that's good. - Yeah. Yeah, I got that.
-但那很不e  -我明白
No, look, it's...
著  那部...
it's really good, actually.
真的很棒
I mean, it's... it's fragile.
我是f  很精致
It's -- it's delicate.
微妙而致
So, where are you from, Kevin Pearson?
你哪睦淼  P文・皮森
Me?
我
Uh... Pittsburgh, originally.
我老家在匹堡
You got family back there?
你的家人在匹堡
Um... not anymore.
F在不在了
Right, so, L.A. is home now?
所以F在你以洛杉榧伊
Yeah, I guess so.
是吧
Yeah.
是啊
I think you should go back there.
我X得你回去
I know, right?
我知道
Are you serious?
你是J真的
I am serious.
我是J真的
And I'm telling you this as a friend
而且是以朋友的身份告V你
because I see this all the time.
因檫@N事我得太多了
I mean, you said it yourself.
你自己也f了
Pretty people come here from TV or movies
演^『碗影的哥美女淼竭@
because they want to do something real.
因樗想睃c真格的
I mean, even if they've...
即便他...
they've never had a genuine moment in their entire lives.
他一子都不曾真\^
Do you know what they find out?
你知道他明白了什么
That guess what?
猜猜看
It's hard.
太y了
It's so hard.
在是太Dy了
It's not...
并不是...
it's not pretend,
不是b出淼
it's not Guys and Dolls in some high school cafeteria.
1955年美著名喜∑
It's not...
不是...
I'm sorry, what-what-what was the-the movie you were in?
不好意思  你演的那部影叫什么碇
It was a TV show, actually,
H上是部
called, uh, The Man-ny.
名叫《n男保姆》
Yeah, and look,
是啊  我f
I'm not saying that
我不是f
you're not good at what you do.
@角色你演得不好
I'm sure you're...
我相信你肯定...
you're great at it.
肯定非常出色
I mean, I-I couldn't do it.
我就演不了@角色
But this... is not that.
但你演『瓦@里是纱a事
You're in over your head,
你的能力不
Kevin Pearson.
P文・皮森
I mean, if you really want to do this, then go home,
如果你真想演@  就回家去
find a class, get some training.
班  W一下
I'm just being honest.
我是f
I see.
我懂了
As a... as a friend.
以朋友的身份
- Yeah. - Yeah.
-是的  -好吧
Still, just, you know, it feels like
可我是X得
you're using the word "Friend" wrong.
"朋友"@~你用e了
Everything all right?
出什么事了
- You okay? - Yeah.
-你好  -好
Yeah?
真的
Yeah.
好著呢
You got the part.
你拿到了那角色
Wait, I'm sorry, what?
等一下  不好意思  你f什么
They think the nanny will sell tickets.
他X得"保姆"硌豳u
It was actually The Man-ny.
其是《n男保姆》
Dad, look! I'm going under and everything!
爸  快看  我要下去了
Dad!
爸爸
- Yeah, I see you, pal! - Randall.
-我看著你呢  伙  -m德
- Dad! - Lunch, baby.
-爸爸  -午
- Dad! - You know, maybe she was just
-爸爸  -也S她只是
- trying to be helpful. - Dad! Watch!
-想忙  -爸爸  看我
By condescendingly telling me how I could raise my kid? Yeah.
居高R下地教我怎么B孩子  就@么兔
- No, thank you. - Dad!
-不了  xx  -爸爸
*I love my father and I love him well...*
*我畚野职  很酆鬯*
*I hope to see him someday soon*
*希望不久后的某一天能到他*
*'Cause where I live  It gets dark at night*
*因槲易〉牡胤  到了晚上又黑又暗*
*The kind of dark eats up the light*
*那N黑暗吞噬光明*
*Yeah, where I live  It gets dark at night*
*我住的地方  到了晚上又黑又暗*
*And you know that, mother*
*你知道的*
*I'd be lying*
*我在fe*
*If I didn't tell you I'm afraid of night.*
*如果我f我不怕夜晚*
Kate, you're not eating.
P特  你怎么不吃|西
You okay?
你好
What's up with her?
她怎么了
Are you kidding me?! Oh! Why?
逗我呢吧  槭裁
Because we didn't make her wear a T-shirt, that's why.
因槲]她穿T恤  就因檫@
No, no, Jack, you're only gonna make it worse.
不  杰克  @只情r更糟
Sit...
坐下
Sit down. Seriously.
坐下  真的
I almost drowned!
我差c就淹死了
- What? - Did you even care?
-什么  -你留意^我
- When? - I tried to get to the deep end,
-什么r候  -我都要到池底去了
- but you never watch me. - Hey. Calm down.
-可你看都不看我一眼  -冷o下
- You always watch them. - Kev, Kev, Kev.
-你是盯著他  -P文  P文
- Come on... - Don't touch me.
-好了  -e碰我
Watch yourself, pal.
心c  孩子
And you're so busy making sure that Kate's not eating too much...
你一直忙著不P特吃得太多
Kev, calm down.
P文  冷o一下
and... and Randall's not too adopted,
要不m德X得自己是被IB的
and meanwhile, where's Kevin?
可@r候P文去哪了呢
Oh, guess what?
你猜猜看
He's dead.
他死了
Bud, we love you. We were watching...
孩子  我勰  我看著你呢
Don't touch me.
e碰我
I got this one.
交o我吧
Hey, come here. Come here.
^  ^
- What? - I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
-干什么  -抱歉  抱歉
I'm sorry.
Σ黄
Okay? I should have been watching.
好  我一直看著你的
- Okay? - You should have.
-好  -你是看著我
And I said I was and I should have been watching you, pal.
我承Je`  我一直看著你
I'm trying, okay?
我在努力  好
Look, I know that I'm bigger than you.
我f  我知道我比你年o大
I know that I'm an adult,
我知道我是成年人了
but I... th-th-this is my first time, okay?
但我也是第一次v@些  好
This is my first time, too.
我也是第一次
I got three of you and I'm trying.
我有了你三  我在努力
I'm sorry. I should've been there.
Σ黄  我本在你身的
And I'm gonna be there, okay?
我以后都在你身的  好
Okay.
好
Can I have a hug?
能o我一肀
Can I get a "Dad, I love you"?
能f句"爸爸我勰"
Do you have the name of a barber?
你有理l的名字
I do.
有
Well, I would appreciate it.
┠愀嬖V我
Then I'll write it down.
我o你
When he gets out of the pool,
他上岸之后
you need to put lotion on him
你得o他涂c乳液
or he gets ashy.
不然皮w灰
Lotion. Okay.
乳液  好的
Thank you.
xx
Do you think that my son could play with yours
我鹤悠r放W后
sometime after school?
能跟你家小孩一起玩
Yeah, yeah.
然
I think we can do that.
]}
And does he need sunscreen or not?
有他到底需不需要涂防
He does, right?
是要的吧
I thought he did.
我X得要
I knew he did!
我就知道
Can you tell my husband that, please?
你能臀腋我老公ff
Uh, I didn't bring a resume, sorry.
我]Шv  抱歉
I didn't think I'd have a job interview.
我不知道要面
And I thought I would just pick up an application...
我以榫褪悄申表
Oh, well, you're here and I'm here, let's talk.
既然都砹  那就聊聊吧
You have really pretty skin.
你皮w真好
Oh, thank you.
xx
So do you.
你也是
So, Kate, do you know anything about my store or my background?
P特  你ξ液臀业牡甑谋尘坝辛私
Hmm... A little.
一cc
I know that you've had this store since 2013
我知道你在2013年_了@家店
and before that you sold your own designs on Etsy,
在@之前你_W店u你的立O
until you partnered with that woman
直到后砟愀人合伙
that you met at UC Santa Cruz--
是你加州大W圣克分校的同W
at her wedding in Thailand.
你去泰⒓恿怂的婚Y
Oh, so beautiful.
太美了
Like, that is my dream trip.
直是粝胫旅
And then you imported those scarves
后砟氵M口了@些巾
then it just, like, took off from there.
生意拇俗呱狭苏
Oh, and you're divorced, you have no kids
有你x婚了  ]有小孩
and you look amazing in wide-brimmed hats.
你戴檐帽的幼犹好看了
I assume.
我猜的
You just have the head for it.
你^型很m合
I don't. I look like a pacifier.
我不m合  我戴著就像奶嘴
I like a person who does her research before an interview.
我喜g面前做足功n的人
I'm a big researcher.
我最做功n了
Hey, what's up?
好
So, the good news is: I got a job.
好消息是我找了份工作
Well, that means that there's bad news.
意思是有南息
Adult swim.
成人游泳rg
Adult swim only.
小孩都上岸
You cold?
你冷
T-shirt?
T恤呢
I didn't bring one.
我]
Well...
那...
I brought a T-shirt.
我Я思T恤
That's the one Mommy hates.
@件
Oh, Mommy's just jealous.
只是妒忌
I don't think so.
我不X得
Well, it's true.
是真的
She just pretends like she hates it
她只是假b
because I won't let her wear it.
因槲也唤o她穿
You know where I got this shirt?
你知道@件衣服哪淼
I heard Mommy say it was from a drugged-out drifter.
我f是a君子流浪h的
Listen, Mommy doesn't know the whole truth,
不太了解情r
so this is gonna have to stay between us, okay?
你e跟e人f  好
I got it...
我r
in Florida.
在佛_里_
A magical land called Daytona Beach.
一叫代托{比奇的神奇的地方
Can we go there?
我能去那
No.
不行
No, you may never go to Daytona Beach.
你不能去代托{比奇
I want you to say it out loud:
我要你大f出
"Daddy, I will never go to Daytona Beach."
"爸爸  我^Σ蝗ゴ托{比奇"
Daddy, I will never go to Daytona Beach.
爸爸  我^Σ蝗ゴ托{比奇
Good girl.
乖
But I was there...
我r就在那
and one night, I was walking back to my hotel,
一天晚上  我在回酒店的路上
and... I came across this man...
然后遇了一人
a traveler.
一旅客
He was wearing ragged clothes
他穿得破破的
and he had a strange way of talking.
口音很奇怪
And these three young jerks were bothering him.
有三牡霸谄圬他
They were trying to take away his bag of groceries.
他想拿走他的一袋生活用品
And so... I chased the jerks off.
所以我把那些牡摆s跑了
By yourself?
你一人
Yeah, by myself.
是的  就我一人
And I had a few...
我之前喝了妆
vitamin drinks and... I chased them off.
S他命料  把他s跑了
It happened.
真事
And the traveler was so grateful,
@旅客非常感激
he wanted to repay me.
想蟠鹞
You know, he-he didn't have much,
但他有的|西不多
so he reaches into his little satchel
所以他把手伸M他的小包里
and he pulls out this shirt.
掏出了@件衣服
He says to me that it's a magic T-shirt.
他跟我f@是件有魔法的T恤
He said,
他f
that when you wear it,
你穿上它的r候
your enemies will see you exactly as
你的κ志看到你希望他
you want to be seen,
看到的幼
and only that way.
而且只能看到那幼
Whether it's a... a warrior,
o你想成槲涫恳埠
or a princess.
公主也好
Whatever you want.
任何形象都行
- Does it work? - You tell me.
-真的有用  -你f呢
I was wearing this shirt the night I met your mom.
我遇你那晚  就穿著@件衣服
And she thought I was the handsomest man in the world.
她rX得我是世界上最的男人
- You? - Yeah, I know.
-你  -是啊
Me.
就是我
Magic.
魔法
I'm gonna go with princess.
我x褡龉主
I want you to know...
你得知道...
that your daddy already sees you that way
就算]有@件衣服
without the shirt, okay? You don't need it.
你也一直是爸爸的公主  你不需要它
Thanks, Daddy, but I'm gonna wear it anyway.
xx爸爸  不^我是要穿著它
Okay.
好啦
Your Highness.
公主陛下
Need to find you a crown.
我斫o你找皇冠
Oh, my God, this is not happening.
老天  @不可能
This is-- are you-- oh.
@事...  你真的...
Toby.
托比
So you're telling me
你是在告V我
that you work for my ex-wife?
你要槲仪捌薮蚬
I didn't mean to, okay? It just happened.
我原]@打算  只是其自然而已
Like, I-I wanted to see her up close.
我只是想近距x看看她
So you... just stalked her like a serial killer.
所以你...  就像Bh⑹忠痈她
Josie and I prefer to call it "research."
誊绾臀腋愿意Q之"做功n"
"Josie and I."
"誊绾臀"
Wha-- how in the hell is there a Josie and I?
怎么又砹"誊绾臀"
I don't know.
我也不知道
- I just had to know. - Know what?
-我只是想知道  -想知道什么
Toby, one of these things is not like the other, okay?
托比  @事ξ碚f比^特殊
So I wondered, like was she fat and then she got skinny?
我想知道  她是不是暮芘p肥成@拥
Was she a terrible person? But no.
她是不是的人  可答案都是"不"
She's actually beautiful, and she's great,
她是那么美貌  出拔萃
and she thinks that I'm great,
她夸我很棒
and she has amazing taste in imported goods.
她o店里M的也很有品味
Like, feel this.
摸摸@
I don't even know what that is!
我根本不知道@是啥|西
It's a portfolio.
是公文包
And I liked it.
我很喜g
Is that what you want?
那N是你喜g的型
Is that what you want? Do you want a skinny person?
是你喜g的  你是不是喜g身材窈窕的人
No, but I would like to be with a sane person, Kate.
不是  不^我喜g和正常人在一起  P特
That is not nice.
@可不好
Yeah, well, maybe I'm a little tired of being nice.
好吧  也S我已φf好倦了
Some stranger tells you that you're great and you believe her.
有陌生人f你很棒  你就信了
I tell you you're great and you think I'm lying.
可是我f你很棒  你就X得我在_你
Why is that?
到底槭裁
I don't... I don't know. I have a problem.
我不...  我不知道  我有}
We all have problems, Kate.
我都有一堆}  P特
Toby, all of my life...
托比  我的一生...
You've been fat.
你一直很胖
Yeah, I get it.
我知道
I empathize, clearly.
我很理解你
I empathize, then I say something cute,
我理解你  所以逗你_心
then you feel better, rinse and repeat.
你高d起  然后又消沉  如此反
She was terrible to me, Kate.
她ξ液茉愀  P特
Josie, this skinny, successful woman
誊  @身材窈窕又成功的女人
that-that you admire so much?
你真的那么崇拜她
She cheated on me, she lied to me,
她出了  她_了我
and then she took half my life savings.
然后拿走了我一半的e蓄
I gained 95 pounds
她x_我一年后
in one year after she left me.
我w重一下L了近九十斤
At my lowest point, I told my brother
在我最低谷的r候  我跟我弟弟f
that I was committing suicide even though that wasn't true
我要自  然那不是真的
because I wanted him to be as scared and lonely as I was.
我只是想他和我一痈械娇趾凸陋
You know what? You know what? That's...
你知道  你知道  其...
That's a lie, I, uh...
我]f  我...
I did consider suicide.
我_想^自
A lot.
很多次
When I would get drunk,
那r候我以酒渤
alone,
形斡爸
and disgust myself.
B自己都鹤约
So, you haven't cornered the market on problems, Kate.
所以  面R}的并不只有你一  P特
God, I'm really sorry.
天啊  我在很抱歉
My issues are not gonna go away overnight, Toby.
我的啦一夜之g消云散  托比
Well...
好吧
neither am I.
我也不
But Jesus, Kate...
不^  P特...
Josie and I
誊绾臀
weren't good together.
以前相并不愉快
So we're not.
今后也不
It's not like I was gonna keep the job anyway.
不管怎  我是要去她那里打工
But you know who are good together?
但你知道l和l相很愉快
Matt Lauer and Savannah Guthrie?
R特・诙和_S{・格思里
I love them.
我鬯z
And I want them to be my family.
我希望他成槲业募胰
And also us.
有我z
We're pretty good together.
我在一起相也特e愉快
But mostly I was talking about Matt and Savannah.
但我主要在fR特・诙和_S{・格思里
Can I keep the portfolio?
我能留著@公文包
Oh, my God, you're killing me.
天啊  真要命
No.
不行
Do you just want to feel it?
你就不想摸一下
Oh, my God.
天啊
What is that?
@是什么啊
That's a baby something.
是小什么的
Leave a message for Kate.
oP特留言
Hey, hey, it's me.
是我
I got the part.
我拿下那角色了
Yay, right? I think.
算是...  很棒吧
Can you call me? Uh, it's just, you know,
能o我回  就是...
you're-you're usually the one who... who tells me how great I am,
一般都是你告V我有多棒
and you're not here.
而你不在我身
So...
所以...
Man, that Tess was some Snow White tonight, huh?
天  苔z今晚演的白雪公主不一般啊
Yeah.
是啊
I've offended you somehow.
我好像冒犯到你了
- No. - No, I have.
-]有  -不  我有
- You think I'm judging you. - I...
-你X得我是在u判你  -我...
Because I'm in no position to judge you whatsoever.
因槲]Y格δ闫奉^足
But you need to know,
但是你要知道
if I was in a position to judge you,
如果我有Y格u判你
you'd be getting a very high score.
那也是很高的ur
That story you told about helping to bus little black kids in Pittsburgh.
那段在匹堡秃谌和上W的v
- That was '86, '87? - Thereabout.
-86年  87年的事  -差不多吧
So you were clean then?
你那r]吸毒
Just... functional?
能正常生活
Because you know what this little black kid was doing?
你知道我@黑人小孩那r的情r
- I don't... - I was a little boy,
-我不...  -我是孩子
living in Bethel Park, Pennsylvania.
住在e州的伯特利公@
Which is pretty much the whitest place on Earth.
那生活的大多是白人
I had this little notebook...
我有小本本
and every time I met a new black person,
每次我新JR一黑人
I would put a mark in this notebook.
就在那小本本上擞一下
And every time I met a black man, I wondered if, somehow,
每次遇一黑人男子  我就心想
if that man could possibly be my father.
@男人有]有可能是我父H
But I couldn't say that.
但我不能f
You know, I couldn't say it out loud
不能f出
because I loved my father.
因槲畚腋赣H
My white father.
我的白人父H
And my white mother.
有我的白人母H
I'm a strong, successful, black man.
我是刃大  事I有成的黑人
My wife and I give a lot of thought
我和我妻子在育悍矫
- to how we raise our girls, believe that. - Yes.
-真的花了很多心思  -我信
The fact that my daughter doesn't find anything unusual
我女翰挥X得自己演白雪公主
about her playing Snow White?
有何不妥
That's the whole idea.
就wF了@教育理念
Right?
Π
Look, I-I don't know everything, William.
我并非o所不知  威廉
I don't.
不是
But I wouldn't change a thing about my parents,
但我ξ业母改负M意
or the way that I parent,
τ悍绞揭M意
- and I will not apologize for any of it. - You shouldn't.
-我不榇说狼  -你也不
- Because I don't. - I should.
-因槲也挥X得抱歉  -我道歉
Three weeks I've known you,
我JR你三星期了
and I still haven't said the words.
我]跟你f那句
- You don't have to say any... - I'm sorry.
-你不必f什...  -Σ黄
I am so deeply sorry.
我非常抱歉
I did everything wrong by you.
我做了Σ黄鹉愕氖
And you've done everything right.
而你每件事都做得很
You are doing everything right, son.
邮伦龅枚己芎  鹤
Well, uh...
那么
Now, you wear whatever you want on your walk tomorrow.
你明早散步r  想穿什么就穿什么
Oh, I like my new flat front khakis just fine.
我挺喜g@l新卡其的
- Baby say what? - Uncle Kevin!
-f啥  -P文叔叔
- How are you? - Good.
-你好  -很好
- How you doing? - I'm good, how are you?
-你怎么  -很好  你呢
- Oh, you look beautiful. - Thank you.
-你真漂亮啊  -xx
Honey, look, it's Kevin.
H鄣  瞧  P文砹
- What's up, bro? - Yo!
-你好啊  弟弟  -你好
- What's going on, man? - Oh, you know.
-最近好  -就那
Missing my fan club, of course, you know?
想念我的小粉z
And, uh, you don't mind if I crash for a bit, right?
你不介意我鹤∫幌掳
- Absolutely. - For a time.
-然行了  -就一段rg
- Yeah. - Thanks.
-行啊  -xx
Uncle Kevin, I was Snow White!
P文叔叔  我演了白雪公主
- Yeah? - You should come see the video, and
-是  -你砜纯磁牡囊l
we have to call Stacy Klein,
我要o史黛西・克R恩打
who doesn't believe you're my uncle.
她不相信你是我叔叔
You're kidding me, that's ridiculous.
不是吧  搞什么啊
All right, yeah, I'll be right there.
好  我R上就^去
We'll tell her what's up.
我跟她打招呼
- She's cute. - Yeah, she is.
-她太人喜g了  -是啊
- Uh, Kevin, this is, uh... - Yeah?
-P文  @是...  -l啊
William, he's my, uh...
威廉  他是我...
This is my biological father.
@是我生父
Whom I looked for, and I found,
我ふ疑父了  找到了
and this is him.
就是他了
Uh, well, that probably is gonna be a longer conversation,
@事得跟我好好聊聊啊
but it's good to meet you.
但很高dJR你
It's a pleasure to meet you.
幸
Uncle Kevin, come on!
P文叔叔  快
- Uh, go. - Okay. All right, yeah, no.
-去吧  -好  我先^去了
- Let's go. - Go, go, go, go. Yes, yes.
-我走吧  -去吧  去吧
All right, where's my little Annie, huh?
我家安妮呢
I miss the other half of my fan club.
我想念另一小粉z啊
Was that the Man-ny?
他是上那"奶爸"
- Yeah. - Yeah.
-是啊  -是啊
I love that show.
我特e喜g那部
I'm gonna go get my autograph book.
我去拿本找他名
Hey, is now a bad time to mention having another kid?
@r候f想再要一孩子是不是不合m
Are you reading?
你在看
I'm on the last page, come on, baby.
我快看完了  我看完吧  H鄣
- Yeah. - Please.
-好  -拜托了
ZiMuZu.tv
字幕M